[
    {
        "Question": "extant",
        "Answer": "remaining",
        "Options": "existing"
    },
    {
        "Question": "extended",
        "Answer": "long",
        "Options": "lengthened/ stretch"
    },
    {
        "Question": "extensive",
        "Answer": "large",
        "Options": "widespread"
    },
    {
        "Question": "extracted",
        "Answer": "removed",
        "Options": "taken out of"
    },
    {
        "Question": "evade",
        "Answer": "escape",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "evaluate",
        "Answer": "judge",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "eventually",
        "Answer": "in the end",
        "Options": "overtime/ at a later time"
    },
    {
        "Question": "ever-shifting",
        "Answer": "constant changing",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "evident",
        "Answer": "obvious",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "evoke",
        "Answer": "arouse",
        "Options": "produce/ promote"
    },
    {
        "Question": "evolve",
        "Answer": "developed",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "extol",
        "Answer": "praise",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "extraneous",
        "Answer": "from outside",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "extraordinary",
        "Answer": "exceptional",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "exude",
        "Answer": "give off",
        "Options": "release"
    },
    {
        "Question": "facilitated",
        "Answer": "made easier",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "faded from",
        "Answer": "disappeared from",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "faithful",
        "Answer": "exact",
        "Options": "accurate"
    },
    {
        "Question": "fastidious",
        "Answer": "demanding",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "favored",
        "Answer": "preferred",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "feasible",
        "Answer": "practical",
        "Options": "achievable"
    },
    {
        "Question": "feat",
        "Answer": "remarkable achievement",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "features",
        "Answer": "aspects",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "first rank",
        "Answer": "highest quality",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "flaw",
        "Answer": "fault",
        "Options": "incorrect"
    },
    {
        "Question": "fleeing",
        "Answer": "running away from",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "flexible",
        "Answer": "adaptable",
        "Options": "bendable"
    },
    {
        "Question": "flourished",
        "Answer": "prospered",
        "Options": "succeed"
    },
    {
        "Question": "fluctuations",
        "Answer": "variations",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "fluid",
        "Answer": "liquid",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "focus",
        "Answer": "concentrate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "foremost",
        "Answer": "earliest",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "formulated",
        "Answer": "developed",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "forward-looking",
        "Answer": "progressive",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "fostered",
        "Answer": "encouraged",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "foul",
        "Answer": "pollute",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "fractures",
        "Answer": "cracks",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "fragile",
        "Answer": "easily damaged",
        "Options": "delicate"
    },
    {
        "Question": "freeing",
        "Answer": "releasing",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "friction",
        "Answer": "conflict",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "frigid",
        "Answer": "cold",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "fringes",
        "Answer": "borders",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "fuels",
        "Answer": "provides energy  for",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "function",
        "Answer": "purpose",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "fundamental",
        "Answer": "basic",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "further",
        "Answer": "additionally",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "furthermore",
        "Answer": "in addition",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "fused",
        "Answer": "combined",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "gains",
        "Answer": "increases",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "garment",
        "Answer": "article of clothing",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "gather some momentum",
        "Answer": "made progress",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "generated",
        "Answer": "produced",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "giant",
        "Answer": "huge",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "gifted",
        "Answer": "talented",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "give rise to",
        "Answer": "produce",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "gradual",
        "Answer": "slow",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "graphically",
        "Answer": "vividly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "gratify",
        "Answer": "satisfy",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "guarantee",
        "Answer": "ensure",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "habits",
        "Answer": "usual behaviors",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "had priority",
        "Answer": "had advantages",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "halted",
        "Answer": "stopped",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "harnessed",
        "Answer": "utilized",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "harsh",
        "Answer": "severe",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "hastened",
        "Answer": "rushed",
        "Options": "accelerated"
    },
    {
        "Question": "heightened",
        "Answer": "increased",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "hemispheres",
        "Answer": "sides",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "hence",
        "Answer": "therefore",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "henceforth",
        "Answer": "from this time on",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "heterogeneous",
        "Answer": "varied",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "hierarchical",
        "Answer": "having several levels of authority",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "highlights",
        "Answer": "emphasizes",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "hints",
        "Answer": "clues",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "his imitator",
        "Answer": "the people who copied hime",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "hitherto",
        "Answer": "at first",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "homogenous",
        "Answer": "uniform",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "huge",
        "Answer": "vast",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "humble",
        "Answer": "modest",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "identifiable",
        "Answer": "recognizable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "illuminates",
        "Answer": "lights",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "imaginative",
        "Answer": "creative",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "imitate",
        "Answer": "copy",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "imminent",
        "Answer": "about to happen",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "immobile",
        "Answer": "motionless",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "impeded",
        "Answer": "restricted",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "impediment",
        "Answer": "obstruction",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "impervious to",
        "Answer": "unaffected by",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "implements",
        "Answer": "tools",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "impetus",
        "Answer": "motivation",
        "Options": "incentive/ stimulus"
    },
    {
        "Question": "implications",
        "Answer": "consequences",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "impractical",
        "Answer": "unrealistic",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "impose on",
        "Answer": "place on",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "improve",
        "Answer": "refine",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "impulse",
        "Answer": "basic motive",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "inaccessible",
        "Answer": "unreachable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "in addition to",
        "Answer": "furthermore",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "inadequate",
        "Answer": "deficient",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "inadvertently",
        "Answer": "unintentionally",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "incentives",
        "Answer": "motivation",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "inclination",
        "Answer": "preferences",
        "Options": ""
    }
]